Rubin "Hurricane" Carter Papers MS226
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Writings, 1970 -- 2012; MS226.009; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - Writings by Carter, 1970 -- 2012; MS226.009.001; 3.6 Linear Feet
    - Speech at Harvard University, 2002; MS226.009.001.012.00024 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at Justice Western Australia and trip information, 2009 -- 2010; MS226.009.001.012.00025 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at Mr. Big Screening, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00026 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at the Canadian Olympic Association, 1990 -- 1999; MS226.009.001.012.00027 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at the International Festival of Arts and Ideas, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00028 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at the Northern California Innocence Project, 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00029 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at York University, 2005; MS226.009.001.012.00030 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech - Brain Dead, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00031 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech - Innocents on Death Row, 2003 -- 2004; MS226.009.001.012.00032 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech - Night of Consciousness, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00033 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech of introduction for Howard McCurdy, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00034 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech on behalf of Al Kareem Sheedad, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00035 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech on Innocence International Inc., 2004; MS226.009.001.012.00036 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
      Includes the laminated copy of the writ of habeas corpus granted to Carter in 1985 that freed him from imprisonment.
    - Speech, partial draft, 2005 -- 2010; MS226.009.001.012.00037 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech - The Death Penalty and Politics, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00038 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech - The Jews and Rubin Carter, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00039 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech to Chicago legislators, 2005; MS226.009.001.012.00040 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech to the New Jersey State Home for Boys - Putting Yourself Together, 2004; MS226.009.001.012.00041 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech to the Progressive Jamaican Association of Canada, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00042 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech to the Texas Mortgage Bankers Association, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00043 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speeches, 1997; MS226.009.001.012.00044 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speeches, 2002; MS226.009.001.012.00045 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speeches, 2008; MS226.009.001.012.00046 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speeches at Innocents Behind Bars Conference, 2002; MS226.009.001.012.00047 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Unfinished talks, 1970 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00048 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - The White Problem in America, 1980 -- 1999; MS226.009.001.012.00049 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
  - Writings by others, 1997 -- 2009; MS226.009.002; 3.6 Linear Feet
    - Federman, Cory, The Body and the State: Habeas Corpus and American Jurisprudence tyepscript, 2004; MS226.009.002.012.00050 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Flax, Amy A. The Rubin Carter Case, 1997; MS226.009.002.012.00051 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Hoksbergen, Al and Dough Tjapkes. Why?, typescript, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.002.012.00052 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Zarlenga, Peter N. "This is the land of the free..." typesript, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.002.012.00053 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)